[
  {
    "question": "Which Bollywood movie is the highest-grossing film of all time?",
    "options": ["Dangal", "Baahubali 2: The Conclusion", "PK", "Sanju"],
    "answer": "Dangal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is known as the 'King of Bollywood'?",
    "options": [
      "Amitabh Bachchan",
      "Salman Khan",
      "Shah Rukh Khan",
      "Ranbir Kapoor"
    ],
    "answer": "Shah Rukh Khan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which actress played the role of 'Geet' in the movie 'Jab We Met'?",
    "options": [
      "Kareena Kapoor",
      "Priyanka Chopra",
      "Katrina Kaif",
      "Deepika Padukone"
    ],
    "answer": "Kareena Kapoor"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who directed the movie '3 Idiots'?",
    "options": [
      "Sanjay Leela Bhansali",
      "Rajkumar Hirani",
      "Karan Johar",
      "Anurag Kashyap"
    ],
    "answer": "Rajkumar Hirani"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Bollywood actor is known as the 'Khiladi' of Bollywood?",
    "options": ["Ajay Devgn", "John Abraham", "Akshay Kumar", "Tiger Shroff"],
    "answer": "Akshay Kumar"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Bollywood movie features the song 'Chaiyya Chaiyya'?",
    "options": [
      "Kabhi Khushi Kabhie Gham",
      "Veer-Zaara",
      "Dil Se",
      "Kal Ho Naa Ho"
    ],
    "answer": "Dil Se"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which year was the movie 'Sholay' released?",
    "options": ["1975", "1980", "1970", "1985"],
    "answer": "1975"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the director of the movie 'Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge'?",
    "options": ["Yash Chopra", "Aditya Chopra", "Karan Johar", "Rohit Shetty"],
    "answer": "Aditya Chopra"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Bollywood actor starred in the movie 'Ghajini'?",
    "options": [
      "Shah Rukh Khan",
      "Salman Khan",
      "Hrithik Roshan",
      "Aamir Khan"
    ],
    "answer": "Aamir Khan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which movie won the Best Film award at the Filmfare Awards in 2020?",
    "options": [
      "Uri: The Surgical Strike",
      "Kabir Singh",
      "Article 15",
      "Gully Boy"
    ],
    "answer": "Gully Boy"
  }
]
